<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mathura - Maps</title>
    <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mathura on Maps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:46:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Govind Nagar</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/govindnagar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/govindnagar/</guid>
      <description>Govind Nagar is a bustling neighborhood that reflects Mathura&amp;rsquo;s status as a pilgrimage city. Many of the shops and roadside carts sell items identifiable to Hindus as sr̥ṁgāra, pertaining to the ornamentation of household shrines and deities. From east to west, the main artery of Govind Nagar connects the Mathura-Vrindavan road to the residential gully that leads to gate three of the Krishna Janmsthan, the dirt road that culminates at the Jawahar Vidyalaya Inter College, the southbound street to the Potra Kund (along the way offering a market alleyway that takes one to the Janmsthan&amp;rsquo;s gate number two), and the northwestern continuation of Mathura&amp;rsquo;s parikrama mārg (which passes by the rāmlīlā maidān before bending east).</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Krishna Janmbhumi</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/krishnajanmbhumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/krishnajanmbhumi/</guid>
      <description>The Krishna Janmbhumi grounds are one of Mathura&amp;rsquo;s main draws as a pilgrimage site. The present complex is quite a sight &amp;ndash; several temples are complemented by a large stage, two series of dioramas exhibiting Krishna&amp;rsquo;s divine exploits (one stationary, the other animatronic), a library, a bookstore, multiple tea and snacks kiosks, and over twenty souvenir shops.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Old Mathura</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/oldmathura/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/oldmathura/</guid>
      <description>I have labeled the dense jungle of neighborhoods extending west from the bathing ghāṭs lining the Yamuna river to the eastern edge of the Mathura-Vrindavan road &amp;ldquo;Old Mathura.&amp;rdquo; This designation is not entirely arbitrary; although archaeological digs to the West of the Mathura-Vrindavan Road evidence centuries-old structures that predate many of those to the east, urban development in those areas was disturbed during periods Mughal and British rule.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Parikrama Marg</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/parikrama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/parikrama/</guid>
      <description>Mathura&amp;rsquo;s Parikrama Marg is a much frequented route for Hindu pilgrims visiting the city, for they believe that completing this eleven kilometer loop brings religious merit. The city circumambulation takes place on foot &amp;ndash; often barefoot &amp;ndash; and depending on traffic and stamina takes three hours to complete.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>