<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gayatri Pariwar - Maps</title>
    <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gayatri Pariwar on Maps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:46:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri Press</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/gayatripress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/gayatripress/</guid>
      <description>There are actually two Gayatri Pariwar operated presses in Mathura. The smaller of the two, located across the street from the police checkpoint south of the Birla Mandir, is responsible for the publication of the Akhaṇḍ Jyoti magazine, the headquarters of which are located in Giya Mandi, a neighborhood several kilometers south of the Gayatri Tapobhumi.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Gayatri Tapobhumi</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/tapobhumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/tapobhumi/</guid>
      <description>Bookstore As the Mathura Gayatri Pariwar is in charge of producing most of the organization&amp;rsquo;s print publications, it makes sense that the Tapobhumi features an impressive bookstore where visitors can purchase them. Yet literature is not the extent of the items for sale: calendars, posters, bumper stickers, keychains, CDs, DVDs, and USB sticks contain excerpts or full recordings of Guru ji&amp;rsquo;s lectures; worship items are for sale, including mālā beads, pictures of Gayatri Devi, incense, havan kuṇḍs, wooden ladles to use with them, and even havan samāgrī and ghee produced at the nearby printing press campus; Ayurvedic medicines are available for purchase, which I have been told are made at the Akhand Jyoti Press grounds.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Shantikunj</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/shantikunj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/shantikunj/</guid>
      <description>Shantikunj is a campus able to accommodate over ten thousand people. Located on the northeastern outskirts of Haridwar, it is a short walk away from some of the city&amp;rsquo;s cleanest riverside bathing spots. Around two thousand employees live and work at Shantikunj, spread among some one hundred offices that perform work such as book sales, the oversight of regional centers, the scheduling and operation of several halls reserved for life cycle rituals, the facilitation and accommodation of foreign visitors, the maintenance of the Shantikunj campus, etc.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>