<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maps</title>
    <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:46:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://maps.nicktackes.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayatri Press</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/gayatripress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/gayatripress/</guid>
      <description>There are actually two Gayatri Pariwar operated presses in Mathura. The smaller of the two, located across the street from the police checkpoint south of the Birla Mandir, is responsible for the publication of the Akhaṇḍ Jyoti magazine, the headquarters of which are located in Giya Mandi, a neighborhood several kilometers south of the Gayatri Tapobhumi.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Gayatri Tapobhumi</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/tapobhumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/tapobhumi/</guid>
      <description>Bookstore As the Mathura Gayatri Pariwar is in charge of producing most of the organization&amp;rsquo;s print publications, it makes sense that the Tapobhumi features an impressive bookstore where visitors can purchase them. Yet literature is not the extent of the items for sale: calendars, posters, bumper stickers, keychains, CDs, DVDs, and USB sticks contain excerpts or full recordings of Guru ji&amp;rsquo;s lectures; worship items are for sale, including mālā beads, pictures of Gayatri Devi, incense, havan kuṇḍs, wooden ladles to use with them, and even havan samāgrī and ghee produced at the nearby printing press campus; Ayurvedic medicines are available for purchase, which I have been told are made at the Akhand Jyoti Press grounds.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Govind Nagar</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/govindnagar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/govindnagar/</guid>
      <description>Govind Nagar is a bustling neighborhood that reflects Mathura&amp;rsquo;s status as a pilgrimage city. Many of the shops and roadside carts sell items identifiable to Hindus as sr̥ṁgāra, pertaining to the ornamentation of household shrines and deities. From east to west, the main artery of Govind Nagar connects the Mathura-Vrindavan road to the residential gully that leads to gate three of the Krishna Janmsthan, the dirt road that culminates at the Jawahar Vidyalaya Inter College, the southbound street to the Potra Kund (along the way offering a market alleyway that takes one to the Janmsthan&amp;rsquo;s gate number two), and the northwestern continuation of Mathura&amp;rsquo;s parikrama mārg (which passes by the rāmlīlā maidān before bending east).</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Gyan Sarovar</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/gyansarovar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/gyansarovar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Krishna Janmbhumi</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/krishnajanmbhumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/krishnajanmbhumi/</guid>
      <description>The Krishna Janmbhumi grounds are one of Mathura&amp;rsquo;s main draws as a pilgrimage site. The present complex is quite a sight &amp;ndash; several temples are complemented by a large stage, two series of dioramas exhibiting Krishna&amp;rsquo;s divine exploits (one stationary, the other animatronic), a library, a bookstore, multiple tea and snacks kiosks, and over twenty souvenir shops.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Pandav Bhawan</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/pandavbhawan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/pandavbhawan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Shantikunj</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/shantikunj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/gayatripariwar/shantikunj/</guid>
      <description>Shantikunj is a campus able to accommodate over ten thousand people. Located on the northeastern outskirts of Haridwar, it is a short walk away from some of the city&amp;rsquo;s cleanest riverside bathing spots. Around two thousand employees live and work at Shantikunj, spread among some one hundred offices that perform work such as book sales, the oversight of regional centers, the scheduling and operation of several halls reserved for life cycle rituals, the facilitation and accommodation of foreign visitors, the maintenance of the Shantikunj campus, etc.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Shantivan</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/shantivan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 10:35:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/shantivan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item><item>
      <title>BSA College</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/bsacollege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/brahmakumaris/bsacollege/</guid>
      <description>B s a s a t entrance
      B s a s a t audience
      B s a s a t dipa
      B s a s a t exterior 1</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Old Mathura</title>
      <link>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/oldmathura/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maps.nicktackes.com/mathura/oldmathura/</guid>
      <description>I have labeled the dense jungle of neighborhoods extending west from the bathing ghāṭs lining the Yamuna river to the eastern edge of the Mathura-Vrindavan road &amp;ldquo;Old Mathura.&amp;rdquo; This designation is not entirely arbitrary; although archaeological digs to the West of the Mathura-Vrindavan Road evidence centuries-old structures that predate many of those to the east, urban development in those areas was disturbed during periods Mughal and British rule.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>